Everyone was asked to prepare the most potent Stedli concoction in their own history!
Janko's potassium water mixed with manuka honey
It's Mom's special drink!
Yes, it's honey.
Two, two, three spoonfuls in a 300 ml container!
Wow, that's neat!
I did it right.
Hey, you did it right.
I was saying before...
I told you it's just the way it's supposed to be.
It's a little thin, but it's the usual taste.
It's true, we didn't add a little Pocari.
It's a good thing we had a little more.
Oh, let's go ahead and do it.
If it's just the two of us, let me go first! Stop it!
We've got this thing about the two of us, and they're trying to make this one last.
Bana.
Costume.
I really want to drink soda.
I really want to drink soda. But I can't drink it.
I can't drink it because the air would accumulate.
This is just my ideal seaweed that I want to try.
Do you put milk in it?
No, Mike.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no.
What's that?
I really want to stage-narrow the milk.
You want to put it all in there or something?
This is not a mix, it's three products, three products.
Three products, three products, three products. Let's mix them in the right proportions.
I had a menu like that at Saizeriya.
It was a menu item at Saizeriya that said, "Mix what with what and it tastes good.
How much was it?
I think the orange juice was less.
I'm sure it's delicious.
I don't like juice, but this was the only one I liked.
Okay, it's done.
Oh, wow.
Looks delicious.
It's a shinsin orange.
Nice.
Bye bye.
Yeah, there's no doubt about it, this is insanely delicious.
Orangina type, too? No, but it's orangina.
But less bitter.
It looks so good!
And there's no matcha?
What's wrong with that?
So the moment you just drank it, it was a stay?
Well, yes, the moment.
If I drink one of these now and dance, does that mean I can stay?
Sure, sure, sure.
Can you give us a song?
Too much negative promotion. Negative promotion when there's too much air.
Well, drink it, then.
I drank the staged-legs.
I'll take one.
I'm out of here.
Song's about to start.
Stop the song.
The song is starting.
The moment it starts...
I'm really gonna get it
I'm really gonna get it.
Why?
I can't. I can't.
I can't stop.
For once in your life.
Give yourself a break.
Try an ametual challenge.
You can do it.
Dance?
If I was going to dance.
Yes, I am.
Please call me about now.
I'm going to miss the first bit.
When it starts.
Oh, please.
Super. Let it go.
We can drink here.
You guys have fun.
That's where it started.
I started drinking at Moneta Turn.
Wait a minute.
You're gonna drink this.
Drink.
Drink
drink
Suzuki's out too.
Oh, no.
I'm having a drink right now.
Let's get excited!
First of all, Trant.
He's singing!
He's singing, he's singing.
That's great.
Oh, but he's in a bit of pain.
Oh, my God.
What's that?
Oh, we're all going to try.
What the hell is he doing? He's lying.
What is that?
That's impossible.
Oh, man, if I started singing, I'd probably be terrible.
Disgusting.
Oh, my God, this is amazing. You're amazing, Mr. Suzuki.
I'm sure it's not.
I'll stop singing first.
I'm only going to drink udon today.
What if he hates me?
Let's make it fun.
What are we going to do?
I'll cower
Yeah, yeah...
Here's my strongest throw-away takeout Jan-arnamin sheet Yakult
It's a classic, isn't it?
I think we all did this when we were kids.
It's a classic!
It's very popular!
What's the distribution? All of it?
All of it?
Oh, my God, this is the best color.
It would be really bad if it was this color.
Well, it's blood yellow.
You'd think it was citric acid.
Citric acid is like this too, right?
Well, it's you, Mariko, who can fool Guy.
Sure, I can fool Mariko.
Oh, you can't fool me with this.
You put it all in?
Yeah, I put it all in.
It's like fruit juice.
You can't fool me anymore.
Okay, it's done!
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's so good, it's so good! It's so good, it's so good!
It's a fruit juice... and it's like... how many of them are there?
All of them!
I put all of it in! It's not like we're firefighters or anything!
It's not like we're firefighters or anything.
If you need more grated cheese, put some more grated cheese.
I'm sure I won't need more grated cheese.
So, why don't you give her some CC instead of Oronami C and see if that increases the amount?
Seriously?
You're not being picky.
Not enough.
I'd like to put a little more Orange Ace in it.
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
With milk! With milk!
With milk! Milk for fucking milk!
What are you doing?
Elementary school kids.
Shouldn't we mix it?
Orona's instructions are piling up.
Yum!
Did it taste better just now?
Kana-chan says everything tastes good.
Try it.
I used to put a lot of it in the drink bar.
But it smells...
It's just delicious.
It's not water if you drink it.
It's just a case of routine, isn't it?
The size of the pudding, the intensity...
What is it?
Thank you for watching.
Okay.
Oh, she's singing.
He's singing.
She's singing.
That's a bio-bite.
BioByte.
He's making all that stuff.
You're making all of them.
He's making everything.
Solo stage.
That's amazing.
A solo act?
I'm starting to run out of repertoire.
Oh, my God.
This is Binahirum.
Oh, my God, this is amazing.
No, it's... it's a little less carbonated than you'd think.
It gets creamier as it cooks.
I drank it, but it wasn't very much.
I don't think so.
It's fine.
A little Metabolho's.
Music, please.
This is good. This is good.
I think it'll work.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I'm thinking about it.
Go for it.
I got something better than this.
What are you talking about?
I'm looking forward to it.